

Contacts

- **Phone** +7 (963)-747-37-32
- Telegram
 https://t.me/stpkk
- Email stipyk1309@gmail.com
- GitHub
 https://github.com/stpkkk
- in LinkedIn

 www.linkedin.com/in/igorstepanov1
- Address
 Russia, Petrozavodsk

Skills

- React
- TypeScript / JavaScript
- Redux Toolkit
- Rest API / Axios
- Styled Components
- Bootstrap
- Git
- Figma

Languages

Russian - Native

English - C1 - Advanced

IGOR STEPANOV

FRONTEND-DEVELOPER

About Me

A frontend-developer with experience in creating web applications using React.

Good knowledge in JavaScript, TypeScript and related libraries.

Paying close attention to details, it's important for me that the code is clean, well-

organized, and error-free.

Great team member, worked both in large team and as a solid developer.

Have an active life position - there are a lot of sports in my life, i love cycling.

Ready to relocate, full time or part time work.

Open to your suggestions and new oppotunities.

Experience

Technomedia (Petrozavodsk) October 2022 - February 2023

Frontend-developer

- Worked in development of web-application "Business insurance calculator" using React, Typescript and Styled Components
- Worked in updating layouts, adding content and SEO optimization to company's main website sysdyn.ru
- Worked in development of functional components for companies projects
- · Admin side development

Freelance December 2021 - October 2022

Frontend-developer, HTML- developer

- Creating website layouts based in template, using HTML5 and CSS3
- Engaged in SEO optimization and website promotion
- · Design creation for websites in Figma
- Development of Adaptive and Crossbrowser layouts

Education

2022 React-developer, "The way of the samurai"

it-incubator React,

JavaScript, Typescript

2021 Jonas Schmedtmann, The complete JavaScript Course:

Udemy From Zero to Expert

JavaScript

2020 Html Academy, Frontend

Html Academy HTML, CSS

2011-2014 Management and Cadastre, Cadastral Engineer

Petrozavodsk State University